Guide to the People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) Research Files
People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) Research Files
- Other Files, 1.5 linear feet
  - Students United Protesting Research on Sentient Subjects (SUPRESS)(Original Box 30, 2 Folders) - 1 of 2 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Students United Protesting Research on Sentient Subjects (SUPRESS)(Original Box 30, 2 Folders) - 2 of 2 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - American Humane Association(Original Box 30, 3 Folders) - 1 of 3 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - American Humane Association(Original Box 30, 3 Folders) - 2 of 3 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - American Humane Association(Original Box 30, 3 Folders) - 3 of 3 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Vegan Outreach - Pro-Animal Org. (PA)(Original Box 32, 1 Folder) (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Birth Defects(Original Box 34, 4 Folders) - 1 of 4 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Birth Defects(Original Box 34, 4 Folders) - 2 of 4 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Birth Defects(Original Box 34, 4 Folders) - 3 of 4 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Birth Defects(Original Box 34, 4 Folders) - 4 of 4 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Foundation for Animal Use in Society (FAUS)(Original Box 41, 1 Folder) (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Maryland Sheep Breeders Association(Original Box 41, 1 Folder) (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - American Veterinary Medical Association (AVMA)(Original Box 37, 1 Folder) (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - La Sociedad Venezolana Protectorade Animales(Original Box 49, 1 Folder) (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - United Conservation Alliance(Original Box 50, 1 Folder) (Box 154, Folder 13)
  - Wildlife Images(Original Box 55, 1 Folder) (Box 154, Folder 14)
  - Rabbit Pregnancy Test(Original Box 58, 1 Folder) (Box 154, Folder 15)
  - Insects(Original Box 52, 4 Folders) - 1 of 4 (Box 154, Folder 16)
  - Insects(Original Box 52, 4 Folders) - 2 of 4 (Box 154, Folder 17)
  - Insects(Original Box 52, 4 Folders) - 3 of 4 (Box 154, Folder 18)
  - Insects(Original Box 52, 4 Folders) - 4 of 4 (Box 154, Folder 19)
  - Nevada Zoological Foundation(Original Box 41, 1 Folder) (Box 154, Folder 20)